好了  轮到我们了
Okay, this is it.
你确定要这么做吗
You sure you wanna do this?
你好  罗斯太太
Hello, Mrs. Ross.
你好  瑞秋先生
Well, hello, Mr. Rachel.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
菲比  快点   快快快
Come on, Pheebs, hurry up! Hurry, hurry!
好的  好的
Okay! Okay!
我的天啊  大家都要结婚吗
Oh, my God! ls everybody getting married?
教堂里不准奔跑
No running in the chapel.
你少跟我来这...
Hey, don't you give me any of your-
你们来这里干嘛
What are you guys doing here?
罗斯和瑞秋给我们留言
Ross and Rachel left us a message.
说要来这里结婚
Saying they're getting married.
你们不是来找他们的吗
lsn't that why you guys are here?
当然是  不然我们来干什么
Yes. Why else would we be here?
怎么样   我们来晚了吗
Well. What happened? Did we miss it?
我们也没赶上
We actually missed it.
这都怪教堂里不能奔跑
Maybe you wouldn't have if you could run in the chapel!
真是太荒唐了
This is insane.
有什么大不了的  又不是真正的婚姻
What's the big deal? You know, it's not like it's a real marriage.
什么
What?
在赌城结婚  只有在赌城有效
lf you marry in Vegas, you're only married in Vegas.
你在胡说什么  在赌城结婚
What are you talking about? lf you marry in Vegas,
-在哪里都有法律效力  -真的吗
- you're married everywhere. - Really?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
随便啦
Oh, well.
我们为什么会躺在一起
Why are we in bed together?
我不知道
l don't know.
你穿着衣服吗
Do you have any clothes on?
穿着
Yes.
-真的吗  -没有
- Really? - No.
但是我们没有...
But we didn't have...
做爱  对吧
...sex, did we?
我不太记得昨晚的事情了
I mean, I don’t remember much about last night,
一切都好模糊
lt was such a blur.
我记得我在笑  一直在笑
l remember laughing. l laughed a lot.
然后  我们没有嘿咻
Then we didn't have sex.
我们真是醉得一塌糊涂
We were really drunk.
幸好没干什么蠢事
l'm glad we didn't do anything stupid.
可不是吗
Tell me about it.
早啊  菲比
Morning, Pheebs.
我的电影正式取消拍摄了
Well, my movie has been officially canceled.
好可惜喔  乔伊
Joey, l'm so sorry.
你要不要吃我的早餐
You want my breakfast?
我沮丧得吃不下了
Too depressed to eat.
得过五分钟后才有食欲
l'll probably eat in, like, five minutes.
所以我只好跟你们回去了
So I guess l'll just fly home with you guys.
-飞机是几点来着  -那我的计程车呢
- What time is your flight? - What about my cab?
我用不着了
l don't need that anymore.
乔伊  你跟我借了车
Joey, you borrowed my cab.
就得负责开回去
You have to drive it back.
我不想自己开回去  太寂寞了
l don't wanna drive back by myself. l get lonely.
你来陪我怎么样
How about if you come with me?
我不晓得  那得开很久吧
I don't know, it's such a long trip.
有你陪一定很棒
That would be great.
我们可以聊天玩游戏
We could talk and play games.
这是让友谊变新鲜的好机会
This could be our chance to, like, renew our friendship.
你要我跟你玩"友谊复兴"吗
Are you asking me to have a "frienaissance"?
是吧
Sure?
好吧  虽然没这个必要  小宝贝
All right. Although, l don't think we need one, baby.
因为我可是一直爱着你哦
l never stopped loving you.
有谁跟盖勒博士夫妇讲到话了吗
So has anybody talked to Dr. and Mrs. Geller yet?
他们有留言给我  应该随时会到
They left me a message. They'll be here in any minute.
服务生呢  我饿死了
Where is the waitress? l'm starving.
这是自助餐
lt's a buffet, man.
我可以把我的钱吃回本了
Here's where l win all my money back!
我有事找你
l gotta talk to you.
好
Sure.
什么事
What's up?
莫妮卡和我昨晚差点结婚
Monica and l almost got married last night.
天啊
My God!
这可是大消息
That's huge!
等等  为什么没找我去
Wait a minute. Why wasn't l invited?
谁要当你的伴郎呢
And who was gonna be your best man?
不许说是罗斯  不准说是罗斯
Don't say Ross. Do not say Ross.
我只是觉得我们还没准备好
Look, I just don’t think Monica and I get ready to get married yet!
你知道我很爱她
You know, l love her and everything....
但看到罗斯他们从教堂冒出来
...but seeing Ross and Rachel come out of that chapel...
我突然惊觉
...was like a wake- up call
我和莫妮卡进展得太快了
that Monica and l are moving so fast, you know.
我要怎么讲才不会让她心碎呢
How do l tell her without crushing her?
就说她不是结婚的料
Tell her she's not marriage material.
什么
What?
女生都这么对我说
Girls say it to me all the time.
相信我  要是她和我一样
And believe me, if she's anything like me,
一定会如释重负
she's just gonna be relieved.
我该怎么跟钱德勒说进展太快了
How do l tell Chandler that it's too soon?
这会让他心碎
It's gonna break his heart.
他一定会觉得我不爱他了
He's gonna think l don't love him anymore.
-你是不爱他了  -我爱
- Well, you don't. - Yes, l do.
很好  我只是在测试你
Good, good. l was just testing you.
我们刚才在聊培根呢
You know what? We were just talking about bacon.
不对  我们是在聊网球
No, we were talking about tennis.
网球比较让人信服
Tennis is more believable.
谢谢
Thank you.
咖啡
Coffee.
怎样
What?
你们要谈谈昨晚的事吗
Are we gonna talk about what you guys did last night?
昨晚怎么了
What do you mean "last night"?
昨晚...什么事都没发生啊
Nothing...uh, nothing happened last night.
罗斯邀我们大家去"观礼"
Ross invited us all to watch.
瑞秋  我们怎么会错过朋友的婚礼
Rach! We weren't gonna miss our friends getting married.
谁结婚了
Who got married?
你们啊
You did.
什么
What?
-我们哪有结婚  -怎么可能  别闹了
- Hello. We didn't get married. - No, we didn't. That's ridi- -
等等...我记得去过教堂
Wait, wait, wait. l remember being in a chapel.
我们醉成那样
They...they would not let us get married
不可能被批准
when we were that drunk.
他们当然会批准
They let you get married when you are drunk.
在赌城结婚的人通常都醉醺醺的
Most people who marry in Vegas are drunk.
我现在就醉了
Now, l'm drunk right now.
早餐不能喝鸡尾酒啊   我在度假呢
l can't have a mimosa with breakfast? l'm on vacation.
你们要怎么办
What are you gonna do?
看来得找个离婚律师了
Well, l guess we find a divorce lawyer.
我想罗斯已经有人选了
Well, l think- -  l think Ross already has one.
这次会免费吧
Now, this one's free, right?
前两次你都付钱了  所以会白送一次
Because you paid for the first two, the third one for free.
尽管笑吧  丢脸的可是你
Laugh it up, but the joke's on you...
因为我们不必离婚
...because we don't need to get divorced.
-只要办理注销就行  -消什么
- We're just gonna get an annulment. - An annulment?
罗斯  手术不算个办法呀
Ross, l don't think surgery is the answer here.
那是你的专长
Oh, that's your thing!
什么
What?
专长  就是你擅长的事情啊
Your thing, your thing. You know,
你是专门离婚的人
You're the guy who gets divorced.
不  我才不擅长这种事呢
No, no, that's not "my thing."
我并不爱离婚
l do not love getting divorced.
你当然爱  这是你第三次离婚
Yes, you do. This is your third divorce.
你爱"离婚"爱到搞不好会娶了"它"
You love divorce so much, you're probably gonna marry it...
然后婚姻破裂
...and then it won't work out,
你又得离婚  离婚男
so you're gonna have to divorce it, divorcing guy.
我醉得好厉害
l'm so drunk.
-你觉得我们应该怎么办  -不知道
- So what do you think we should do? - l don't know.
但我知道我爱你
But l know l love you.
我也知道我爱你
l know l love you.
那我们现在
So where are we
对"要不要再去结婚"的想法是什么
on the whole "going back to where they have the marriages" thing?
我爱你
l love you.
问得好
That's a good question.
昨晚我们让骰子决定
Last night we let the dice decide.
也许应该再把决定权留给命运
We should leave it up to fate again.
我爱你
l love you!
有征兆  我们才结婚
We don't get married unless there's a sign.
这样
So say...
要是你又掷出个八来
say you roll another eight, then there's a definite sign...
-就表示我们绝对应该结婚  -好的
- ...that we should marry. - All right.
八就结婚
Eight we get married...
但二  三  四  五  六  七  九
...but 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9,
十  十一  十二  我们就不结婚
10, 11 , 12, we don't get married.
听起来不错
Sounds great.
有人要来试试手气
Hey, we got a shooter.
请下注
Money, please.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- Ready? - Ready.
来个八吧
Come on, eight.
没错  来个八吧
Yes, yes, eight.
八  三五八
Eight, easy eight.
真不敢相信我扔出个八
l can't believe l rolled an eight.
真是太不可能了
That was so unlikely.
那我们就结婚吧
Well, let's get married.
唯有这样啦
l guess.
这不是双四八  我昨晚掷的是双四八
That wasn't a hard eight! Last night l rolled a hard eight.
说得对  这个八不对
That's right! lt was the wrong kind of eight.
不能结婚了  真可惜
No wedding! Damn it!
人家超想结婚的
l wanted it so bad!
-去收拾行李吗  -好
- Wanna go pack? - Yeah.
我们这么做没错吧
We're doing the right thing, right?
当然没错
Of course we are.
我们让命运决定了
We left it up to fate.
如果我们应该结婚
lf we were supposed to get married,
一定会有明确的征兆
there would be a clear cut sign.
好  你还剩十九个问题  要好好把握哦
Okay, you have 19 questions left. Use them wisely.
快点  乔伊
Come on, Joey.
你不问就...不能赢了
You can't win if you don't ask any questions!
-怎样啦  -你说回程之旅会很好玩
- What? - You promised me a fun road trip.
结果我们上路六个小时
But we've been on the road for 6 hours,
你就睡了五个半小时
and you've been asleep for 5 and a half.
咱俩在下一个休息站换手
We are switching at the next rest stop,
你给我一路开回去
and you are going to drive the whole way back.
这是对你的惩罚  贪睡鬼
That will be your punishment, you greedy sleeper!
好啦  知道了
All right, all right.
现在你得唱歌给我听
And until then, you are going to sing to me...
因为收音机坏了  你又很自私
...because the radio's broken and you are selfish,
但歌声却很好听
but you have a nice voice.
-真的吗  -快唱
- Really? - Sing!
我想彻夜摇滚
l wanna rock 'n' roll all night
天啊  这一路真的好漫长
Man, this is a long drive.
我的眼睛有睁开吗
Are my eyes open?
没有
No!
早安
Morning.
-嘿  -嘿  老公仔
- Hey. - Hey, hubby.
其实我...
Actually, I...
是想找你讨论注销婚姻的事
l wanted to talk to you about that whole annulment thing.
我不打算去办
Yeah, l'm not gonna do that.
好
Okay.
那我们就维持婚姻关系
So we'll just stay married.
没错
Yes, exactly.
我会请大家叫我盖勒太太
And l will make everyone call me Mrs. Geller.
真是太棒了
Wow, this is so amazing.
我还以为得加把劲才能说服你呢
l really thought l'd have to talk you into this more.
好吧  我现在怕了
Okay, see now l'm scared
因为你好像不是在开玩笑
because l don't actually think you're kidding.
我不是啊
l'm not kidding.
你看  我
Look...I, I...
我不能有三次失败的婚姻
...l can't have three failed marriages.
我不能  明白吗
l can't, okay?
我不要当那样的人
l, I am not gonna be that guy.
搞什么啊
What? So...
所以我们要永远这样下去吗
So, what, we just stay married forever?
这对你有什么影响吗  说真的
Okay, look, how is this going to affect you, really?
我是说  偶尔填表格时
l mean, you fill some form out once in a while...
不能选"未婚"那项
...instead of checking the box "Miss,"
转选"已婚"那项
you check the box that says, "Mrs."
就在"未婚"旁边
lt's right next to it.
抱歉  你说得对  其实嘛
Okay, I'm sorry. You're right. Y'know what?
我们确实是应该结婚
We absolutely can stay married,
因为我之前误会以为
because I was under the impression
那两项离得十万八千里远呢
that the boxes were far away from each other.
好吧  听着
OK. All right, look, just please,
麻烦你静下来
take a moment here...
想一想  你在要求我做什么
...and think about what you're asking of me. Okay?
我不过是要求你帮我一个小忙
l am asking you to do me a favor.
你是在要求我  当你的老婆
You are asking me to be your wife.
而身为我的老婆
And as my wife,
你应该帮我这个忙
l think you should grant me this favor.
飞机上那个小孩踢我踢得真用力
That kid kicked me really hard on the plane.
谁让你扯他头发呢
Well, you did pull his hair.
谁让他拿我的零食
He took my snack.
-我不想再争了  -好吧
- l'm not getting into this again. - Okay.
不过说真的
All right, you know what?
疼死我了
Hurts really bad.
我就叫你不要走路嘛  来
Well, l told you not to walk. Here.
来  我抱着哈
There. There. Okay.
-这不是新娘抱吧  -不是
- This doesn't mean anything, does it? - No.
你怎么可以随便让人搭便车呢
How could you pick up a hitchhiker?
他搞不好是强...
He could be a rap- -
强暴犯或杀人犯什么的
He could be a rapist or a killer or something.
你以为我没有先问过他吗
Don't you think l asked him that before he got in?
我懒得理你
You know what? l'm not talking to you.
睡你的觉去吧
You go back to sleep.
-你是强暴犯吗  -不是
- And, you, are you a rapist? - No.
你喜欢车上小游戏吗
Do you like car games?
喜欢  你知道车牌游戏吗
Yeah, you know the license plate game?
我最喜欢车牌游戏了
l love the license plate game!
我也要玩  我也要玩
l'll play. l'll play.
不行  你需要睡眠  晚安
No, you need your sleep. Night- night.
听着  我知道你想跟我谈谈
Listen. l know you wanted to talk to me...
但我有个办法
...but l have an idea
或许能让你愿意维持婚姻关系
that may make you wanna stay married.
我们去注册...
We register...
礼物通通都给你
...and you get to keep all the presents.
不行  罗斯  你听我说
No, Ross, come on. No, listen.
我一直在想  要怎么表达
Look, l've thought a lot about how to tell you this, and...
罗斯  反正无论如何...
OK. The bottom line, Ross...
我们不能维持婚姻关系
...is we cannot stay married.
-那可不一定  -当然一定
- l don't know if that's true--  - Oh, but it is.
好吧  你知道这叫什么吗
Okay. You know what this is?
这叫做意见不合
This is a difference of opinion.
在婚姻中遇到这种状况...
When that happens in a marriage- -
罗斯  拜托  这不是...
Ross, come on! This is not...
罗斯  这不是婚姻
This is not a marriage!
这是全世界最惨的宿醉
This is the world's worst hangover!
罗斯  如果你不去注销  那我自己去
Ross, listen, if you do not get this annulment, l will.
好  我去就是了
All right. All right, l'll do it.
谢谢
Thank you.
对了
Hey, hey. Uh...
你说会不会有注销婚姻庆祝会呢
is there...is there any such thing as an annulment shower?
停车  停车  火车站到了
Oh, wait, wait! There's the train station.
我该下车了
This is where l get off.
我有你的住址和电话号码
Well, l have your address and phone number.
我知道你的名字和你居无定所
l have your name and the fact that you're a drifter.
看来主动权在你手上
So ball's pretty much in your court.
好  再见  菲比
All right. See you, Pheebs.
拜托  菲比  我受不了了
Come on, Pheebs, l can't take this anymore.
求求你跟我说话吧
Please talk to me.
至少让我补偿你  好不好
Let, let me make it up to you, uh?
* 地面控制中心呼叫汤姆少校 *
* Ground control to Major Tom *
* 倒数开始  发动引擎 *
* Commencing countdown Engines on *
* 吞几颗蛋白质丸 *
* Take your protein pills *
* 戴上头盔 *
* And put your helmet on *
-这是  -闭嘴  够了
- This is- -  - Stop it! Stop it! No!
不公平
That's not fair.
你明知我无法抗拒那美妙的歌声
You know l can't resist that beautiful voice.
菲比  我真的很抱歉
Pheebs, look, l am so sorry.
我答应让你有一段愉快的回程时光
I know l promised you a fun road trip with your friend...
却没能做到
...and l didn't deliver, okay?
但现在我知道
But..but now l know that you think
你认为在友情中  保持清醒很重要
being awake is an important part of friendship.
只要我们还是朋友  我就会一直保持清醒
So l will strive to stay awake for as long as l know you.
你晚上还是可以睡觉什么的
You can still sleep at night and stuff.
谢谢
Thank you.
那可以玩"二十个问题"了吗
So can we play 20 Questions now?
我想到一题很棒的
l got a good one.
在堪萨斯时就想到了
l have been thinking about it since Kansas.
好吧
Okay.
是
ls it...
一种热食三明治吗
...a kind of hot sandwich?
对
Yes.
是肉丸潜水堡吗
ls it a meatball sub?
真不可思议
That is incredible!
你是大师
You are the master!
有虫子
Bug!
真有意思
Ah, that's funny.
-你看起来就像...  -别说了
- You look like you're- -  - Don't say it!
想都别想
Don't even think it.
不说就不说
All right.
钱德勒  你们俩就慢慢耗吧
Okay, Chandler, enjoy your handful.
我们要不要干脆结婚算了  你看现在
All right, Should we just get married? You know, I mean...
所有的征兆都是叫我们结婚
Should we just do it when all the signs are telling us to do it.
我才懒得管那些征兆呢
l'm sick of the signs.
-这样太快了  我对现状很满意  -我也是
- It's too fast. l'm happy the way things are. - Me too.
-我不想改变  你想吗  -不想
- l don't want change, do you? - No.
好  那就不要改变
All right, then. Then nothing changes!
一切照旧  一切维持现状
Everything is grenn, everything stays the same!
你快去整理行李
You go unpack.
已经三天了  我都要被逼疯了
lt's been three days, and it drives me insane!
别激动  又不是结...
Jeez, relax, it's not like we're mar- -
我在想  要是我把行李放这里
You know, l was thinking, what if l...
会怎么样
...unpack here?
那你的东西都会在这里
All your stuff would be here.
那
Well...
要是我的东西都在这里呢
...what if all my stuff was here?
那你就得整天跑来跑去
Then you'd be going back and forth all the time, I mean.
这没什么意义
Doesn't make any sense.
好
Okay.
要是我们同居呢  你懂我的意思了吧
What if we live together, and you undertsand what l'm saying?
同居
Live together?
又没有任何征兆
There've been no signs for that.
我问你就是个征兆
Me asking is kind of a sign.
-好  好  好  -好的
- Yes! Yes! Yes! - Okay.
好的
Yes.
好  你等等  等着哦
Okay. Okay, wait. Wait, wait, wait. Okay.
这是你的钥匙  给你
Here's your key. Here's your key.
现在出去  开门试试
Now go out and christen it!
出去再开门进来
Go out and come back in!
这扇门五年没锁了  不过好吧
Door hasn't been locked in five years, but okay.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- Ready? - Ready!
有个问题  钥匙断在锁里了  我进不去
Okay, one promble, the key broke in the lock, and l can't get in.
等等  天啊  我也出不去了
Wait. Oh, my God, l can't get out!
-这不是征兆吧  -不不不  这不是征兆
- This isn't a sign! - No, no, no! It's not a sign.
-是钥匙太旧了  -钥匙太旧了
- It's a very old key! - lt's an old key!
旧的不得了
Oh, my God, it's old!
我爱你
l love you.
我也爱你
你现在有抱着门吗
Are you hugging the door right now?
没有
No.
好  我也没有
Yeah, yeah, me neither.
注销手续办得还顺利吗
So did everything go all right with the annulment?
嗯  没问题
Oh, yeah. No problems.
都办好了
lt's all taken care of.
罗斯  谢谢你
Ross, thank you.
你们要不要去看场电影呀
Hey, Do you guys wanna go see a movie?
-好啊  -菲比去吗
- Yeah, why not? - Pheebs?
不了  眼前就有一出
No, thanks. l've already seen one.
我去穿毛衣
Okay, l'm gonna get my sweater.
想不想听一件奇怪的事
You wanna hear something weird?
当然
Always.
我没去办注销
l didn't get the annulment.
什么
What?
我们还是夫妻
We're still married.
不要告诉瑞秋  待会儿见
Don't tell Rachel. See you later.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
钥匙断在钥匙孔里
Key is stuck in the lock.
我会修  等一下
l can fix it. Hold on.
让开  让开
Watch out, watch out.
还是不行
lt still doesn't work.
我还没弄完
l'm not finished.
漂亮  乔伊  你真是个好手艺
Nice job, Joe. You're quite the craftsman!